My keyboard was disconnected.
Now it works.
Alright, there we go.
It's Friday.
Today!
Cheers.
Oops.
Oh yeah.
How's everybody doing, huh?
Tell me about your day, people.
What plans do you have for the weekend?
How are you feeling?
Hey, Gollum.
Love from Denmark.
Thanks for joining.
Got Cerulean.
Ibrahim Raffi.
I don't know how to say the last part there.
Hi.
What's up, Journeysend?
I'm working right now.
Lol.
Fish.
What's up, dog-header?
Yo, what time is it in Denmark?
It's five o'clock in the afternoon.
A Google Street View car drove past me today, so I might be on Google Maps.
And now my phone activated, because I said Google.
I actually hate that feature.
It keeps activating at the worst times.
I replaced the drainage on my washing machine.
Very exciting.
The cardinal, that sounds like you did something great today.
Something that needed fixing, right?
And you did it.
Well done, you.
Oh yeah.
Okay.
This right here is Oliver.
He has a antler on his head and a turtle pet.
But don't let that fool you, because he's out for blood.
Why do I have a fish in my hand?
Man, it's been since Monday last time.
I've been so busy with all kinds of things.
Just couldn't find the time to sit down and play this for a long time.
Feels good to be back in, though.
I honestly have no idea what I was doing last time.
Let's think.
I was building, I believe.
I finally got this pylon to work, and I tried and failed many times trying to kill the Wall of Flesh.
I remember that.
Oh yeah, I discovered all the islands.
Well, most of them anyway.
I think there's maybe more here.
And then I put the golfer up here.
That's right.
I did that.
Lion Pines.
A guy who's had the same name throughout all this time.
Which is kind of a rarity, I think.
Now we've had, we've got Seth.
The newest guide in town.
All the other ones.
I did it.
I killed him.
But it was all in the name of something great.
Sort.
Let's see here.
Let's sort these items here.
Also, let me move this.
Also there.
Harpy Banner.
No, thank you.
Oh yeah, right.
We've got stuff like this.
Radio thing.
That's the thing that makes the world darker, but I'm not quite sure what the point of that is, other than that.
There's probably, there's gotta be a secret with that somewhere, right?
That's my thought on that.
The Hornet Staff.
Yeah, I wasn't a big fan of the Hornet.
I tried being Oprah last time.
Didn't quite work out the way I thought it would.
It was a bit underwhelming.
Oh wait, this is a weapon.
Put this in here.
There we go.
Oh wait, this is the magic missile.
This is the goaded weapon.
Put this in accessories.
Fish.
Oh yeah, I did a bunch of fishing.
Found a shit ton of crates and all that.
Shrimp.
Chicken noggin.
By the way, I need food.
I need food.
Why don't they put my... Wait a minute.
I have potions in here.
Wait a minute.
Why do I have all this stuff in here?
Oh, this is the miscellaneous one, right?
The burger.
I'm gonna be needing that.
Crate potion.
Sure, I'll keep that for now.
Banners I believe I have here.
Put that in there.
The jellyfish is also bait.
You know what?
Put the fishing stuff in here for now.
We don't need that.
Not right now.
The chicken nogget.
I'll take that with me.
So let's do a magnet.
Crate potion also goes in.
No, actually this is the down below.
Well, if I can find the thing I'm supposed to find.
I spent a lot of time last time trying to find that and I never did.
The doll.
Shrimp goes in here.
Come on, this flamelash.
What was this again?
Oh my god, I'm so sorry Al.
I didn't see you there.
Is this slower?
Yeah, it's also a little bit slower.
18 man... Bro, this thing sucks.
Magic missile gang rise up.
Let's put this in weapons.
Because maybe I... Can I actually... Is this a material?
It is not even that, but I'll keep it for now I guess.
The magnet.
Seth, remind me about the magnet here.
What was the point of this?
Celestial emblem.
Cuffs.
Flower.
Wait.
Isn't that similar to the one I already have?
Wait a minute.
Oh!
Oh, it's opening it.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
This is worse.
Why would I want this?
Isn't the mana flower way better than the celestial magnet?
Oh wait, never mind.
It's this one.
I'm an idiot.
There we go.
I need to... Okay, so it's the map.
I can actually make this.
Right?
I can make
that.
Avenger emblem?
I don't think I know.
Oh wait, is that related to the waves?
Speaking of, I need to do that.
I'm doing that today.
I'm fucking that shit up today.
I'm telling you now.
It's happening.
So we should be able to do this.
Yeah?
Magnet flower.
Pick up range for sure.
This is not a material, so it's just straight up better.
Awesome.
That gets rid of one more material.
I love it.
Let's actually check if we... Geboto!
Did you sell anything useful?
Right, this one.
Weapon emboomment flasks.
Ah, I don't know how that works.
I tried figuring that out.
I had no idea what was going on.
I remember that now.
I think I put it here.
At that house in the desert.
I can make... Alright.
Potions.
Let's see here.
I need to... Dude, I need to be able to grow my own shit.
I've been saying that for ages, but actually, you know what?
Let's do that right fucking now.
Let's grab some wood.
Do I have wood?
Oh no, it's time to look in all the chests to figure out where I put it.
Probably not there, right?
Oh yeah, what is all this?
Oh my god, I have all kinds of things in here.
There's no way for me to remember what any of these do.
Or what combinations there are.
I have to try them all again with Seth.
This one is actually kind of cool.
Sandcastle.
Places of sandcastles.
I don't know why I would want to do that.
For fun maybe.
Just for fun.
Wood!
Perfect!
And platforms?
Do I have that?
I do have it.
That's lovely.
So here's my plan.
Oh wait, I don't even need platforms because they go on the wall.
They go straight on the wall.
I need to talk to Rosalva because she sells planters.
Actually, let's do that right now.
Do I have money on me?
By the way, is there anything in here?
Oh my god, I have all kinds of things.
Hold on.
Loot all.
Quick stack.
Precise I kind of forgot about that.
This doesn't go here.
It actually goes here, which is a bit confusing.
Skeletron mask.
Maybe it.
Deerclops.
Okay, we've got slimes.
Royal gel.
Slimes become friendly!
Hey, actually!
Wait, what is this?
Red one?
Oh, it's the ginger beard.
Let's just put this on for now.
Slimes are friendly.
God, I have so much crap in my inventory.
Go in here and click...
Godly mace.
Wait, I have eight oysters?
Cool.
Minor improvements?
Nah.
Sort, deposit all, and then grab the ones we want.
I want this.
I want that.
Slow Star Fury.
Wait, when did I get this?
That seems pretty good.
I'm gonna try the material.
Scorpion radio thing is just wild.
Okay, and then we also have this one.
We hide it.
Oh my god, that's a bunch of shit.
Let's sort that inventory.
Put it all in here.
Frogleg.
I'm already like exhausted just from the inventory management.
And it's been like, what is it, 10 minutes?
Fishing, put this in here.
Cactus, put it here.
Shiverthorn, also here.
Sure, fishing there.
Oh, Frogleg in here.
Mana potion can stay.
In fact, all these potions can...
Why is there a star symbol on my... Oh!
Oh, to star it, I guess.
That makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay, do that as well.
This is a material.
Put it in here, I guess.
Now, the star fury.
Was that just another ingredient for that crazy sword?
Yeah, okay.
All right.
Actually, hold on.
Let me see this.
Huh!
It really does cause stars to rain from the skies.
It's not consuming my stars.
Are the stars aiming?
Oh, my god!
Dude!
Dude, that's actually not bad.
Isn't that kind of good damage?
But I guess it's kind of useless down below, because there's no heaven there.
Not bad!
That's pretty cool.
I like it.
But I think my weapon of choice for all this is... hold on.
I wonder, what if I put a candle here?
Why can't I put it?
Will enemies spawn here?
Let's see what happens.
We have candles here now.
It's an experiment.
And it kind of looks cool as well.
Let's put it there.
There we go.
Okay.
Parsec pals.
I really like that name.
That's actually a great name.
I kind of want to use that name for something.
Sounds like a great name for a podcast.
Mushroom.
Let's go in here.
Last is construction.
Let's see if my bags are empty now.
Empty?
Oh, my god.
Okay, not quite empty.
I have an armored celestial magnet as well.
I have all kinds of shit.
Nope.
Noodle.
And now, quick stack.
There's my stars.
I feel like I had more than that, though, but that's okay.
Door.
Let's delete that.
Gravity banner.
Put it here.
The hundi... houndioshudios.
These names are something else.
Oh, man.
I don't even know what... Yeah, here, I guess.
Look at all the crap I have.
Should I be experimenting a little bit here with different weapons against this boss?
Maybe it's not a bad idea.
Balls.
Now, these are kind of bad, but this one could be good, I think.
I think this one has potential to be good.
What about my gear?
I'm using the magic stuff.
That's good, because I want to be sapping, also.
I also have to try the bee grenades.
The bottled water goes in the potions.
There.
One apple.
That's minor.
Nah.
Where's my food chest?
Didn't I have a food chest?
Maybe I ate all the food.
Ah, here it is.
Cook fish.
See the world for what it is.
And then this goes in here.
Why not?
And there.
Whatever.
Just fucking throw it away.
Get it out of my sight.
All right.
I think we got it all.
Should we bring... See, the statues and stuff are kind of useless, because we're going to be running a lot.
And we're going to be running out of range of these things anyway.
There's really no point to that.
All right, fine.
It's time that we descend once more into the depths, because I have a Hensa Pluck with a certain somebody down there.
Sup, Hailey?
See ya, Hailey.
Also, let me utilize the thingy.
Oh!
Wait, what?
Oh, yeah, right.
I have this.
Let me see if I can gain speed like this and then switch.
No, I lose the momentum.
I go down here, I believe.
It's a good spot to do it.
Ah, man, it feels good to be back in this game.
Also kind of weird.
Being back in a 2D game after like five days.
It is kind of a slow weapon.
You know, like, it is slow.
Maybe I should... let me just default again.
I mean, if you think about it, the rate is sort of similar there.
It's not really that much better.
Wait, did I not bring my return potions?
Oh, I need those.
I absolutely need those.
Yeah, I need return.
That's a sick potion to have.
Sonar builder.
You know what?
Maybe we can try and build something down there.
Battle potion, night owl, immiscibility, feather fall.
Wait, gills.
Oh.
Hold on, is this better than actual healing potions?
Restores 100 life.
Wait a minute.
We're going to have to do some testing there.
Yeah, we're going to be doing some testing.
Where are my potion of returns?
They are not here.
Did I use them all?
Maybe I did.
Let me check the miscellaneous chests here.
Sort.
Did I really not fake them?
Or maybe I did use them all.
Sort these.
Okay.
Dude, I have a lot of crap, huh?
Oh, you know what?
Let's try this now, since we're here.
And let me also put my money in.
I wish I would just automatically put it in.
Isn't that the point of something like this?
Oh, the imp!
Got to do that.
Good thing I went back anyway, actually.
They have two of them now?
Perfect.
Good, good, good.
And then I need to talk to... Oh, the tavern guy is not here anymore, is he?
Ah, shit.
Okay, I guess we'll be waiting with that.
That comes later.
Later, alligator.
So what does this do again?
Automatically use mana potions when needed.
Pick up range from mana stars.
Uh, because it reduced mana cost.
Yeah, I think that's good.
But then again, this right here, the fleeting magi luminescence is actually the best.
thing ever.
I really don't know what I should be replacing here.
Maybe the... No, the Brain of Confusion is amazing.
I can't remove that.
This one is also amazing.
But I guess this is only the acceleration part of it, right?
I'll do some experiments.
In any case, I need to find a doll first.
Which is kind of annoying, because I guess I'll have to spend a lot of time trying to find that, and it's not even guaranteed that I can make it.
It's just going to be another death, you know?
Because this game do be brutal.
Okay, here we go.
We're falling down into the underworld.
Here we go.
No matter what, I think it's great for me to go left first.
Because if I, if I have to start it, I have to start as much left as I can.
So I give myself more than enough room.
You know?
Okay.
Okay, let's see here.
We need to find some enemies.
And I guess they would mostly hang out near the houses, right?
That wouldn't make the most sense to me.
And I have a bunch of Obsidian Potions, so I can just eat one of these right now.
Perfect.
Also, I got to be careful here, because they will carry these dolls around.
And if I shoot them down without thinking, the doll can actually fall into the lava by accident.
So I should limit my usage of the magic missile.
Also, should I be sure?
Nah.
Oh, there we go.
We got one here.
Hey, come here.
Give me that.
Perfect.
I kind of want to find some more, just in case I fuck it up.
Oh, I forgot the key again.
That was one more chest down here that I never got.
God damn it.
Gosh, darn it all.
Yeah, I feel like I should... See, this is my plan.
What?
How did I just die?
I have no idea how I just died.
Maybe I just didn't pay attention to my HP.
Is that really what happened?
What the fuck?
Ah, god damn it.
We got to summon these guys again.
Bro, I have no idea what just happened.
I guess... Yeah, please stop summoning.
Thank you.
I guess I completely forgot how much damage I'm taking down there.
Okay.
Ah, he stops running when you open the map.
Oh, I can't reach it.
That's annoying.
At least we got the... We got the doll.
So, success, I guess.
We got what we came for.
I excavated this entire place.
Because I'm a real G.
Yeah, I take a lot of damage.
Is it?
Why am I taking so much damage?
Do I not have very good defense or something?
Maybe I'm just playing careless.
That's probably what it is.
Die if I got the key again!
Fuck!
It's okay.
All right.
Anyway, what I was saying, I want to use the builder potion.
And then I want to cover up areas that are hard to traverse.
So, just the big lava lakes down here.
That's the plan right now.
Because I don't... Do I have flipper potions?
Actually, I do actually have a couple flipper potions.
But, you know, they're not perfect.
But they are nice to have in a pinch.
Uh...
There.
Drink that.
Let's not die.
Randomly now.
Jesus.
So, it is using bottled honey.
Let's see.
Life regeneration is increased.
I wonder...
Damage me, damage me!
Quick!
Bro!
Why are they doing so much damage?
Okay.
Yeah.
I feel like it's not that great.
I mean, the effect is gone now, but I don't know.
It's also only 80, right?
Okay, so I'm gonna make a bridge here.
Builder potion?
Let's try this, actually.
I guess I can just use platforms.
I have some... Whoops, where did it go?
Fuck!
Where did it go?
There.
Let me put it here.
Hey!
I don't know if that's quicker or not.
I can't quite remember, honestly.
Let's just cover up these big areas that are very hard to traverse.
And the thing is, here's the thing.
When I jump around in the air and I hook everywhere, it actually also makes it harder for me to hit.
Because I have to aim like this, you know, instead of just aiming straight.
It's just...
Oh god, I'm lazy.
I don't want to do this.
It seems insane to me.
I'm doing all this just to beat this stupid ass boss!
You're not gonna kill me, are you?
In fact, I'm making a little tunnel here.
Get rid of this.
Oh god.
Oh, I'm actually dying.
Just these random enemies.
Like, think about it like this.
Oh my god, I ran out already.
Oh lord.
I'm gonna be spending so much time.
Think about it like this.
This whole area that I just covered, I'm gonna be traversing in approximately 0.7 seconds in the game.
That's how futile this is.
Nah, you know what?
Fuck this shit, I'm not doing that.
Hey!
Who are you?
Undead Miner.
Interesting.
Huh, what are you doing here?
Oh my god, I'm taking so much damage.
I feel like I'm taking way more damage than usual.
Am I crazy?
Maybe I am crazy.
Like, I'm constantly low HP here.
Get rid of all this.
Please get away from me.
Is it just me, or are these helpers of mine kind of useless?
They do almost no damage.
Okay, at least...
You know what?
The good thing about the Magic Missile is the explosion on impact.
It does a lot.
Where's the platforms there?
Okay, I'm gonna platform this place right here.
Every time there's lava like this,
just do like that.
And okay, this place is also kind of bullshit, I guess.
Oh, I made a staircase.
No!
Don't make staircase!
Okay, fuck it.
I guess I was just gonna start here.
I need to regen first.
So, I guess I gotta wait a million years.
I guess I can find some more dolls while I wait.
Let's do that.
Let's be on the look.
I'm gonna zoom out for this.
We can actually see what's happening.
Hello?
Any dolls?
Did I reach the...
Oh yeah, I did.
Okay.
So, I don't think there's gonna be any more that way.
They gotta be close to the houses.
That's what makes sense to me.
Come on.
Where are the...
Like, there's enemies everywhere, usually.
But when you want them to be here, there's nowhere to be found.
What actually happened here?
What's up with all these torches?
Did they just place blocks?
That was so confusing.
Okay, here I can regen.
Okay, I'm full health.
I'm actually full health.
We can try now.
Yeah, let's try now.
I'm gonna go to the left here.
And then we gotta potion up.
And we're gonna eat our buff food.
And we're gonna do all the things.
All the things.
In fact, I'm gonna go even more to the left.
Last time, I had to dig my way through a couple times.
But now, those paths are open.
That's nice.
Did I just...
What did I just take damage?
Little flying fuckers again.
Okay, this one is bullshit.
I'm gonna cover this one.
There we go.
I still have the...
I don't have the protection on right now.
I think we're good.
What do I want on?
I think my items are good.
It's time for attempt number 47.
Shine...
What is this again?
Sure, why not?
Let's emit an aura of light.
Why the hell should I not emit auras of light, huh?
Flipper, obsidian skin, magic, missile, magic power, thingy.
Burger, major improvements.
Hunter, I think I want restoration here, actually.
And I think that's it.
Oh my god, I'm taking damage.
Where's time?
Oh my god, there's a guy there with the thing!
Don't do it!
Okay, okay, we're fine.
Okay, that's nice.
We got two attempts now.
That's awesome.
Now if they would just stop coming over here, because I need to regen HP before this.
Zoom in a bit.
Okay, here we go.
Look at all the buffs I have, huh?
This is it, man.
This is...
Oh yeah, okay, get ready with the grenades as well.
I want to try these.
Honey, everything is good.
Oh, you, get away.
Clear the area.
Uh, I think we're good.
Let's go.
Wish me luck.
Oh no, he didn't go in.
Seth, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, it has come to this.
It needs to be done.
Did I just fucking throw both of them in there?
For fuck's sake.
Try the grenades.
God fucking damn it, man.
Hey, this magic missile is stupid.
Here, eat some grenades.
These grenades do nothing.
Oh my God.
I'm not doing any damage to him.
Renates!
Bro, these grenades suck.
Am I hitting anything?
I need to zoom out, otherwise I can't see.
Okay.
I'm hitting him...
I'm hitting him in the mouth.
I think that's good.
Either that or the eye.
I'm gonna try and hit the eye.
Oh, actually, fuck.
Kinda hard to hit, actually.
Kill these goddamn tentacle thingies.
And now when we're low on mana, we switch to the thing.
Let's try and hit the eye.
Oh my God, he's doing a lot of damage.
Okay, I'm doing...
I'm actually doing decent damage here.
Guys, this is pretty good.
Oh, he's shooting lasers now.
Oh, fuck, I'm stuck.
Yep, come on.
Oh my God.
Don't you fucking hit me with that.
Get it!
Job!
I'm almost dead here.
Oh, I think this is it.
No!
Oh my God.
This fucking boss, dude.
Fucking hell.
I am so tired of this fucking boss, dude.
Ah, there goes the fucking dolls, both of them.
Oh my God, man.
All right, let's make these again.
This time, let's try and grab the key while I remember.
Shadow key.
Let's make it unique.
Fuck the obsidian door.
Nobody wants obsidian doors.
Um, what did I want now?
Right, the thingy.
No!
Where did it go?
Did it go in here?
There it is.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, we try again.
Well, we got to find another doll.
Actually, hold on.
Didn't she sell some kind of...
I want to try something, actually.
Ma'am?
Oh yeah, sunflower, actually.
We can use that.
Oh no, we can't!
We can't plant that shit!
This is what I wanted to try.
Can I even purify that fucking beast?
Or something?
Make it a little easier.
This is just crazy.
God damn.
I actually wanted to buy the planters as well, but I'm going to do that later.
It's just...
I don't know.
The system for planting things is very weird.
And I don't know, cumbersome, it feels like.
Like, if you click the wrong button, you accidentally destroy the plant.
And it's just...
I'm not understanding it, man.
It gives me a headache.
All right, go down here.
Okay, I'm going to go right now, because there's a bunch of houses.
Hopefully, we can find another doll.
Whoop!
Oh wait, we're not here yet.
Yeah.
I haven't explored much to the right down here today.
Get away from me.
I do wonder why they carry around these dolls.
And why the guide specifically, right?
It's very mysterious.
Get rid of this fool.
There we go.
Okay, see this right here.
This needs a bridge.
Holy shit.
That is just...
What the...
Oh, there we go.
Like, look at this stretch of lava right here.
Hellish conditions.
Okay, nice.
That's better.
Let's get rid of this door, because I hate that I have to open it to get through.
It's actually annoying me.
You know what?
Keep doing it like this.
Go more to the right here.
Can't believe I'm doing all this fucking work just to kill this boss.
This feels like I'm playing Fortnite right now.
Actually, I've never played Fortnite, but I know you can do stuff like this in Fortnite.
I've seen these crazy videos of people in combat just fucking building things.
It looks so silly.
Okay, let me keep going from here, because this is...
Look at this stretch of lava below me.
Wow.
Yeah, there's no way I'm trying to fly through this part.
Actually, I'm running out of platforms now.
Oh, here we go.
What's happening?
Leave me alone.
I need to make more.
Jesus, look at this place.
Here, here.
Make a shit ton of platforms.
Okay.
What if my minions accidentally kill one of those things with a doll and the boss just gets summoned?
Please go down.
Get away from me.
Ah, my finger.
Ah, here we go.
Leave me alone.
Wondering how the enemies...
Oh, sort of spawn on top of the stuff I make here.
They're like, oh, nice.
A place we can walk on.
Let's spawn here.
Hellbat Banner, Magma Stone.
What's that?
Melee attacks inflict fire damage.
Huh.
Cool.
All right.
Not bad.
I can try giving that to Seth.
Well, I guess Seth doesn't exist anymore.
Seth is dead.
I'm going to use up all these platforms.
I'm going to try hard this shit so much.
Because I'm tired of dying.
Hey, I'm building here.
It looks so funny when he's building.
He's just moving his arm in a loop.
Like he's absolutely slapping down these platforms.
Oh, there's something funny about that.
Okay, leave me alone.
This is fine.
Okay.
Well, now we just need to find a goddamn thingy here.
Easier said than done, of course.
Zoom out.
I don't see anything there.
Is he up?
I don't see anything here.
Ah, no.
That's just a normal one.
Daddy needs a doll.
I need it.
What happens if I...
Summon it all the way over here?
I wonder if I'm on the second half of the map if it will go left instead of right.
It would be kind of weird if I summon something over here and it pushed me to the edge, right?
So that's my theory.
If you're on the...
Oh, no.
Oh, no, shit.
Get up.
Oh, my God.
Fuck.
Oh, no.
Welp.
Actually, not the worst because now I don't have to walk all the way back again to the left.
Nah, that's just copium.
For sure.
Where's my thingy?
There it is.
All right, summon more of these.
There we go.
There they are.
All right.
All right, people.
We go again.
We go down and try and see if we can find a demon so we can have a chance to fight the guy.
Okay.
I wonder if I can make a pylon inside down here.
If I can, I want to do that.
Dude, what if I, in the middle of the fight, use a potion of return?
I heal up and I come back.
I wonder how that would work.
Does the boss just keep going right?
Does he stop when I'm gone and just waits for me?
Or is he gonna despawn?
I don't know.
That would be a cool test.
Although I don't have a potion of return right now.
But I would try it if I had one.
Maybe I should try to go west down there again.
That is where I, after all, found the two of them today that had one.
Maybe they respawned.
In that area.
You know what, I'm gonna consume one of these.
Because I don't want to just randomly die again.
I think that would be wise.
Get rid of these doors.
Come on, demons!
Where you at?
Why are there no enemies now?
All of a sudden.
What's that?
Murderous demon side.
What does murderous mean?
Damage, speed, crit.
All right.
I don't think there's anything this way, dude.
It's gotta be over here.
It's gotta be near these houses.
Although I seem to remember also getting a doll from somewhere not down here.
At all.
Like somewhere upstairs.
I just can't for the life of me remember where that was.
Maybe I can craft them.
Because I'm able to craft other items that summon bosses, right?
Maybe there's a way to do that.
Also, hold on.
Let me actually try something.
Oh yeah, I'm way too slow on the exit.
Nah, nah, nah, nah, man.
We need deflating.
Absolutely we need that.
Holy shit.
Hold on, speaking of speed here.
Do I have a potion of swiftness?
I feel like I should have that.
That would be kind of useful.
What are you shooting at?
I see.
Who's who's that?
Ah, it's just a bat.
Flaming bat.
Oh, what do we got?
Hey, there we go, there we go.
Gimme.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
That's what I'm talking about.
Well, get away from me.
Okay, so what I'm going to do now...
I'm going back.
I want to craft some more potions.
Let's see here.
Give me the water.
Now, once again remind me...
how this fucking shit works.
Iron skin, I have.
Swiftness.
Blink root cactus.
Gotcha.
I think I have all that.
Cactus.
And...
Blink root?
Water... no.
Do I not have it?
Wait.
Blink root.
Perfect.
I got it.
Let's make five of these.
And...
Let me also see here.
Man, what else could help me?
Regeneration potion.
Daybloom mushroom.
Let's see.
Yeah, make four of these.
And then...
What else?
I'm doing absol...
Wait, wait, wait.
Greater healing potion.
Whoa!
Oh, right.
I need crystal shard.
Fuck!
How do I get that?
This would be a game changer.
Oh, man.
Also, I forgot I had food buffs.
I need to utilize that.
Max life...
Yeah, that one.
Oh, I can't make that, of course.
What is wrath?
Increases damage.
Oh, but I don't have that either.
Fuck.
I tried to find an Ebon koi.
I couldn't find it.
I think I have to get that from the waters of the crimson area.
I can't see...
Or maybe actually fishing in the underworld or some...
Obviously some kind of special biome, right?
So it's all about which one that could be.
Do I have more magic power?
I do, perfect.
Mana regeneration would be...
Actually, that's not really needed.
Thorns, deathweed and cactus.
I can make that one, at least.
Where's deathweed?
Is it up here?
It is, great.
Vicious spreads the crimson.
I don't want to do that.
Or maybe I do.
Maybe I just want to fuck up this world.
Okay, now click on this.
Get rid of all that crap.
Now, all these stars...
Speaking of all the stars falling here, actually.
Maybe I want to try the other weapon I have.
Because I have so many stars that I don't use anyway.
Maybe it's worth a try.
I have the star cannon.
A couple of stars falling here.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Give me this star as well.
Maybe I'll just try going ham.
Okay, I think we are good.
Sword items.
Does this look fine?
It looks okay to me, at least.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Potion of return.
Let's see if we can make one of those.
Water.
Ah, now how did that look?
Potion of return.
What?
Teleportation.
Mining.
Fuck, I have no idea where it is.
Uh, I wish I could search.
I can't see it.
Life force.
Teleportation.
I can't see it.
Wish I could search.
I'm just going to give up.
I'm trying to find that right now.
All right, we go back now.
We got to take it the manual route.
Maybe I even have a potion of return somewhere in my 19 million chests.
But honestly, I can't be arsed to look through that.
I need to find some system to manage this inventory problem.
Some system that works, because this is clearly not working for me right now.
I wonder what that system could look like.
Maybe the system is to...
Fuck, I can't even think of a system that would work very well here.
Maybe just have a more, what do you call it, precise categorization of items.
So like a chest, just the potions only like I have now.
And then a chest only for wood.
And then only for stone.
But it's like so much work to figure that out.
A good organizational system.
I don't know if I even want to do that.
Let's see, do I have my...
Where's it?
Good.
I have the doll and I have everything else.
I think it's time.
Also, where's that gun I got?
Let me quickly try this again.
I mean, it shoots kind of fast, you know?
I mean, yeah, we can try that a little bit, I guess.
Does it do... hold on, does it explode on impact?
Hold on.
Maybe it does.
If you notice, it's sort of this...
Oh, hold on.
It's a little bit explosiony when it hits.
Maybe that can help with all the ads.
That's what I thought the B potion would be great for, but it seemed to do nothing.
Okay, I think this is a good spot to start it.
Or hey, actually, maybe I want to start it more to the left.
Because it does seem to speed up at some point, right?
Maybe I want to save that speed up until I get to these platforms here.
So up until then, I can sort of chill a little bit, you know?
All right, I'm burning.
Let's fix that.
There we go.
Like this area here, this would be fine to just bullshit my way through, you know?
There's no problem there.
This is fine.
But like when he starts to speed up a little bit, that's when things get a little tricky.
Like this is very bad to traverse.
Okay.
Also, notice how the biome sort of changes here.
With these things hanging from the ceiling.
Okay.
We only have one doll on us right now.
So we can't mess it up by throwing two of them.
That's something.
Magic power?
Chicken nugget?
Hunter?
Flipper?
Then we need iron skin?
Shine, whatever.
Regeneration?
Swiftness?
Thorns?
Sunflower can't be placed because we need...
I think dirt.
Get away from me.
What else should I be doing here?
Oh, hold on.
Is everything in order?
Pure... pure...
What happens if I...
Yeah, purify!
Okay.
And then...
I think we're good.
Obsidian is on.
All right.
Go!
Fuck you!
Yeah, come on.
Oh, it's really slow in the beginning, actually.
Maybe it's like a gradual increase in speed.
Maybe it's not like at some point.
It's like...
Oh no!
I actually need ult-tap for a second.
I'm back, I'm back.
That was scary.
Okay, let's actually try this weapon.
Oh, that is not bad.
But it's kind of hard to hit with it, I guess, when there's obstacles in the way.
So let me do this first.
Shoot!
Shoot the eye.
That's doing decent amount of damage, but honestly, I think this is even better.
Oh god, I'm not hitting shit.
Oh god, we've got demons!
Hit him!
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
This is so far, it's so good.
We haven't even reached the platforms yet.
Here we go.
These are the platforms.
Let me, let me...
Whoa!
Let's go.
Oh, I ult-tapped again!
How am I doing that?
Twice in a row here.
What's happening?
Oh god, dodge these.
Okay.
Oh, this thing is coming after me.
Oh, dodge.
Okay, here we can heal a little bit.
Oh my god.
Go on.
Hit him.
Okay, we've got some more platforms here.
Okay, he's speeding up now, he's speeding up.
He's speeding up.
Okay, this is nice.
Oh, I'm taking a lot of damage from those lasers.
Come on, hit him.
Oh, he's shooting fast.
Oh my god.
Oh my lord.
Wow.
Jesus, what is that?
Hold on, I need to calm down a second here.
Jesus Christ.
Hold on, I did something when I ult-tapped.
What did I do just now?
Okay, I thought for a second, maybe I accidentally closed everything down.
But I didn't.
Everything is still intact.
Okay, calm down for a second here.
What did we get?
Treasure bag.
Fuck yeah.
I was half expecting like a cutscene or something right now.
What is this?
What the fuck?
Why is there...
Why did this little...
The thing spawn here.
That's weird.
Crimp taint brick.
Huh.
Huh, that's interesting.
It's just like normal crimp taint, but it looked different, didn't it?
Dude, maybe I freed Seth from the curse or whatever.
Actually, I don't know what his name is now, but...
Okay, I gotta...
First of all, open this.
Please leave me alone for a second.
Deposit all.
Grab this.
Let's try and see what's in here.
Own hammer.
What?
Demon heart.
Whoa!
No way.
Wait, what is...
Hello?
Thank you.
Heart star cloak.
Okay.
What else did I get?
Brisk sorcerer emblem.
Magic damage increase.
Laser rifle.
Is that good?
Ah!
That's very quick.
Very fast speed.
Not bad at all.
I like it.
The own hammer.
80% hammer power.
Strong enough to destroy demon altars.
Really?
Huh.
All right.
Oh, this thing is...
pretty good.
Although it does use a lot of mana.
Okay, okay.
Awesome.
Now the demon heart.
Oh, it's a consumable!
No way.
Oh!
Dude, that's big!
Soul of light!
Finally I got a soul of something!
My god!
Hold on, I need to...
You know what?
Let's fuck out of here.
Because we're not done looking at this.
Okay, hold on now.
15% increased magic.
I like that.
So this now does 43.
And this one does 68.
From 61, I believe, before.
Pretty solid increase.
Living fire block.
Hard star cloak.
Causes stars to fall after taking damage.
And a plumber's hat.
What?
Okay.
Uh, all right.
Wait, did I use all my...
No, wait, I put them in here, didn't I?
My stars.
Wait, what?
Did I get that?
Just now?
Summon Skeletron Prime.
I put all of this in here.
I guess I got that.
What the fuck?
Okay.
Uh...
All right, summon.
All right, who are you now?
Asher!
Talk to me now!
Is there something I can help you with?
Did you feel a change?
In your personality, maybe?
Or a change surrounding your curse?
Huh, maybe not.
Powerful wizard who lives in these parts?
Make sure to keep an eye out for him next time you go on the ground.
Really?
Have I found him already?
Hold on.
Maybe I...
I'm not sure.
I hear there's a woman out there well-versed in fighting back the forces you just unleashed.
Maybe if you prove yourself, you can get her attention?
Wait, what did I just unleash?
The fuck are you talking about?
Happiness?
You're fond of wandering, I know.
Stylist?
The tortured soul down in the underworld sure looks familiar.
Have you tried using purification powder on him?
What did I want to try earlier, huh?!
Bro, I'm a fucking genius.
Remember?
I brought this down there to try and throw on the wall of flesh and be like, away with you!
Purify!
But it's probably not this guy he's talking about, right?
That's awesome.
There have been some pirates sighted around lately.
If we befriend one, you think he might show us where he buried his treasure?
Okay, so you know what I think here?
He's suddenly seeing all these new things.
Maybe every time you beat a boss, that's what updates the guide.
And he's like, well, obviously, he's the guide, right?
So he's going to give you the next step.
So I guess beating wall of flesh was like the big thing I had to do, right?
So there's pirates sighted around lately.
If we befriend one, you think he might show us where he buried his treasure?
I've heard of glowing mushrooms growing big enough on the surface to gain sentience.
Wonder if there's any truth.
Wait, what?
Where?
I've been all over the surface.
Have I?
Yeah, yeah, I have.
Actually, there's one place I haven't been.
I haven't actually been down here yet.
Oh, dude, I should try it and dig underneath the sea.
Have I not?
I haven't even tried that.
Dude, why have I not tried that yet?
I feel like that would be like a thing I would try, but I guess I didn't.
So I have a water candle here, increased monster spawn rate.
Yeah, maybe we get rid of that.
It's not a good idea to have that water candle here.
Nope.
By the way, speaking of water candle.
Asher, what can I do with the water?
Oh, it's not a material, nevermind.
But can you?
No, okay.
All right.
Get rid of this.
So the soul of light.
Talk to me!
Key of...
I need 15 souls of light.
Are you kidding me?
Deo of pow.
Yo, that's a very good melee weapon.
Melee weapon, sorry.
Cool whip.
Wait a minute, isn't that an American condiment?
Or something?
Isn't that something you put on a sandwich?
Your summons will focus struck enemies, strike enemies to summon a friendly snowflake.
Let me have some of that cool whip.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
And a sky fracture, that sounds cool.
Light disc.
Greetings, programs.
Dude, I only have one soul of light.
Do I need to kill 15 of those walls?
Can I even kill it again?
What the fuck?
Okay, well.
Well, well, well.
What else did I get here?
So I can do this?
Hold on, Skeletron, isn't that the guy I already killed?
Skeletron Prime, is that different?
I don't remember what his name was.
The old man.
The cloak.
Nope, not that one.
What's this?
Mana cloak.
Ooh, I can make that now.
Wait, can I?
Bee cloak, because it starts to fall, releases bees, and douses the user in honey when damaged.
Wow.
Okay, okay.
Wow, you can really become a bee person.
If you want.
That's amazing.
Causes stars to fall and increases length of invincibility after taking damage.
I mean, that sounds pretty good.
Especially for someone like me who takes a lot of damage.
But I don't have a cross necklace.
Can I not make this?
Did I put it in here?
Oh, wait, I made this.
But does that count still?
I wonder.
No, wait, this is not a material.
Do I have another mana flower?
I feel like I got multiple.
Didn't I?
Maybe it didn't.
Snake charmer's thingy.
Immunities of curse.
Hmm.
I don't remember.
Maybe it didn't.
Okay.
No!
What else can you tell me?
Living fire block.
Oh.
Okay.
I can make a...
blocks that light up, it seems.
Could be cool.
The plumber's hat.
I kind of want to put that on.
Wait, why am I not...
Oh, it's because I have this one on.
Get rid of that.
I want to look like Mario.
The precise bone helm.
Let's put this one.
Is that a material?
It's not.
Put it in here, I guess.
Oh, why did I just put it in?
No, keep that for now.
I'm going to need to knock back the fire.
Hmm.
This one is actually not that great.
If you think about it, this one could easily be replaced.
Right?
That's not that great.
At least I don't think so.
Okay.
By the way, the soul of light.
We could make a key.
Key of light.
We need 15 for that.
I think that key goes in one of the chests I found here.
Remember, we found a bunch of chests in this area that we never found the key for.
So this one has to go into one of these, is what I'm thinking.
Yeah.
Now, Azure.
What a beautiful night.
With your recent victory, the world seems more at peace.
And these lanterns are in celebration of that.
But, hold on now.
Didn't you just tell me I just unleashed something?
Unless you meant that I unleashed the lanterns.
It's like you're contradicting yourself here a little bit.
I think I saw a treasure map floating around in the ocean once.
But a shark ate it.
Maybe you should go try and find one.
Bro, say no more.
I was hidden there anyway.
Let's try that, actually.
Let me go check that out.
Also, Driskan.
I kind of need to speak to you.
Have you seen any me-burrs around here?
I have not.
I don't even know what that is.
Uh, give me two of these.
Because I want to try this again.
And... Mortal.
Would you rather have a bullet hole or a grenade hole?
That's what I thought.
Oh, well.
Wait, explosive powder.
Isn't that new?
I'm gonna try that.
Thank you.
I'll be taking that.
Okay.
Let's go up here.
Oops.
Here we go.
This place is so weird.
God, I'm so happy I finally beat that stupid boss.
It feels amazing.
It's the same feeling I have right now after beating a really tough section of Rainworld, you know?
Is that really sweet feeling of victory after so long of failure?
It's the best feeling ever.
Has that moon always been there?
That green moon?
Am I noticing new things here?
Izzy?
I might have a job for you.
Don't think you can say no either.
Well, in that case...
It's a whale!
It's a dolphin!
No, it's a penguin fish.
Oh, not again.
Surface tundra?
I don't want it.
Hey, what's that up to?
Have you...
Have you talked to me by chance?
I have not.
Oh.
What do you...
What's that?
Rubble maker.
Dolphins.
Calm down.
Let's see here.
Can be placed.
Used with materials to place matching rubble.
Right click to toggle placement size.
What?
Rubble maker.
Well, I'm...
Mummy?
Excuse me?
Mummy mask.
The mummy is new.
I haven't seen the mummy.
Eat the cake.
Um...
I should have brought my gills.
Shit.
That was the one thing I wanted to do.
I need gills.
I have gills potion.
I have it right here, actually.
Look, five of them.
Breathe water instead of air.
And I have a flipper one, don't I?
Or did I use that?
Let's try the water walking as well.
And this one.
This one can be deleted.
Actually, what I want to do right now.
I want to do something very nice.
Where's the empty...
Where's the water bottles?
I don't know where I put them.
Did I put them here?
I did.
All right, Ash.
Asher.
Water bottle.
Bottled water.
I want to make...
This.
Ah, I can't!
I need chaos fish for that.
I need to really figure out how to get all these items.
Where the heck am I gonna find chaos fish?
In a chaos biome.
But that seems to me like...
This one down here.
Right?
Isn't that the closest thing to chaos?
Anyway, now that I got the Eternia crystal, I can try this real quick.
Before I go back to the east.
And I also have my thingy.
There.
Let's try this now.
Once again, we try this.
You know what?
Can I put it up here?
On top of Hailey's house?
Well, how about we do that?
The Eternia crystal rejects this area and pops away instantly.
Yeah, okay.
Fine.
All right.
That's fair enough.
Actually, the spot I was in was kind of decent.
I mean, this spot right here is actually okay.
There we go.
What?
Really?
Wait, where did I put it before?
Oh, is it because I built a house for Hailey?
Maybe...
Probably what's happening here, right?
Okay, what's the large flat area?
I don't even see one.
Could I just make my own?
Let's see here.
Mud?
I have a lot of mud.
I could use mud, I guess.
Or stone.
Dirt.
Let's use dirt.
Let's make it...
Actually, maybe the desert will be fine.
Let's try that.
Nah, it's not that flat, is it?
Will this count?
Maybe this is...
Okay, we'll see.
Please get rid of that shit.
Dammit!
Grape!
All right.
Get rid of this crap!
There we go!
It's happening.
Probably not the best spot, actually.
Oh, I have an idea.
Bees!
Wait!
Wait a minute, this is different.
Oh, is it because I'm in the desert, maybe?
Different...
It's like biome-specific.
That's actually kind of cool.
I should just be standing up here, actually.
Bees!
How do you like them, bees?
Ethereum Goblin.
Oh, man, I think I'm going to fail this.
This is already kind of difficult.
And we're at the very beginning.
What the hell?
Why is this so much more difficult?
Are we done?
Next one?
Ethereum Mana.
Huh.
Wait a minute, I kind of want to try this one some more.
Laser them down.
And as soon as we're empty, we switch.
Probably should have used my potions here as well.
Bro, this weapon is actually decent.
Yeah.
It's nice.
It's actually way better than what I have here.
Or not way better, but it's definitely nice.
Oh, mysterious portal.
That's where they emerge.
Cool.
Also, this one is helping.
Brisk Sorcerer Emblem.
For show.
Let me actually drink this.
And also...
I think we're okay.
Oh my god, this weapon is amazing.
Look at that guy.
It's a big ogre.
Ethereum Javelin Thrower.
Oh, don't you throw that shit at me.
Oh!
Oh, they are throwing now.
I think I'm getting overrun.
Oh, something just dropped.
Oh my god.
No.
Peace!
Oh my god, the beasts do almost no damage.
This is a little difficult.
Okay, here we go.
Next wave.
I'm gonna save my fast weapon until they're close.
Or someone that's flying.
They're easier to hit with that.
Ah shit, I gotta hit.
Oh my god.
Jesus Christ.
I'm fucking dead here.
This is not gonna work.
Am I being bombed?
Someone's bombing.
Oh my lord.
Jesus Christ.
I need to heal.
Oh, I'm not surviving this.
It's all ogre.
Peace.
I'm gonna save the beast when things get really hairy.
Okay, things are hairy.
Peace for everyone!
Oh, hell nah, dude.
It's all over.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
What the fuck?
This event is fucking ruthless.
I cannot win this.
It's too hard for me.
Wow.
Then again, I didn't even put down my healing lantern and stuff like that.
So I wasn't fully buffed, you could say.
I kind of missed a bunch there.
Yeah, I was kind of underpowered for that.
Well, I'm gonna try that in the future when I'm even stronger.
Clearly not strong enough, or at least I don't have the skills.
I really want to get rid of this one, but it's so good that I want to keep it, you know?
I can't believe I got an extra accessory slot.
That is huge.
That makes me think maybe I can get even more.
And I want it.
I want it bad.
I want all the accessory slots.
I got defender medals.
In fact, I already have some of those.
How many?
I don't remember.
Maybe like 10, I think.
I had some somewhere.
There, look, 10.
Now I have 12.
Okay, someone's...
No, I don't want to do that.
I don't know what the next...
Okay, so he said something about the water, right?
Let me go to the water now.
Let's go look in the water.
So I'm going here, and we go up.
Now we have gills.
So we can become a fish, swim with the dolphins and all that.
Juice!
This guy has a ton of HP.
What the fuck?
I feel like a lot of stuff changed after that fight.
Am I crazy?
Like, I've never seen someone with 500 HP.
This is kind of annoying to get up here.
It's fine, it's fine.
We got it.
Okay, here we are.
Actually, we kind of look nice.
Purple and red.
Okay, it's gills time.
Yoink!
Let's check it out.
What do we got?
Is there something down here?
If there's nothing here, I want to dig down.
That's the plan.
Superior Trident.
Increases mobility in water when held.
That's right.
I remember that now.
We got one of these before.
Yeah, much better.
Get out of here.
Gills!
And a recall.
Cool.
Oh, and this is the end.
That's it.
Can't go any further there.
So, I want to try and go down here now.
Oh, am I crazy or...
Is there a huge arrow in this thing pointing towards this chest I'm on right now?
Look.
The arrow's pointing straight to the chest.
Oh, wait.
That's not the pickaxe.
Pickaxe time.
Put that...
There, I guess.
I'm actually going to do something smart here.
What just damaged me?
Oh, I can't put the sand because it's sand.
But I can do that.
And then...
Ah, fuck.
Hold on.
Actually, I can breathe.
Ah, stop it.
I can't dig...
Okay, this I can do.
There we go.
That's what I was looking for.
Do I have lights?
I do.
Oh, I see something.
Actually, wait a minute.
Let's quickly...
Where's my void bag?
Open this.
Deposit all.
I see something here.
I want this.
Let me have another kills.
Because why not?
What was I looking for?
Did I not bring my danger sense?
Oh, wait, no.
Hunter?
Location of enemies.
Didn't I have a danger sense spelunker?
Oh, let's take that one.
Oh!
Toxic sludge!
Let's check that out.
Look at that.
It looks happy as hell.
All right, give me this.
What is that?
Zoom out.
Possessed armor!
Excuse me?
This is the edge, by the way.
Like, that's why the screen is not moving to the right.
This is the edge of the world.
What the fuck?
What are these guys doing here at the edge of the world?
Have some water.
Sup, dude?
How about you?
Dude, he has a ton of HP.
He went off to the edge of the world.
All right.
Cool.
God, this is so slow.
Give me my other pickaxe.
Ah, much better.
Toxic sludge, I'm coming for you.
You seem to be trapped in here.
I have not seen you before.
How are you doing?
He was doing fine, I guess, until I came along and ruined his day.
Okay, now I just want to keep going down like I did before.
Let me go back up here.
Like that.
Keep going down.
Did I have a mining potion on me?
I don't think I did.
Could have made one.
Oh, there's something here to the right.
Another cave.
But that's the edge of the world.
I don't want to go right.
I want to go to the left a little bit, actually.
Oops.
Oh, we've got a heart there.
Man, I really thought that would be something crazy underneath the ocean.
And again, we aren't that deep yet.
Oh, wait!
I'm fucking dying!
Let's just drink another one of these, huh?
For safety.
Who's that?
Possessed armors.
They're hanging out near the edge of the world.
Okay, I'm draining.
Here we go.
I see treasure.
Somewhat.
Night owl potion.
That's actually nice.
I want that.
Thank you.
Give me blink root and all that.
Wait, I'm just going to go exploring here.
Didn't I also have a shine potion?
I did.
Let's shine it up.
Thank you.
Wait, what is that again?
It's tin.
Oh.
I haven't been mining these things forever.
I kind of forgot what they look like.
What's that?
It's kind of good to just mine again.
You know what I mean?
Oh, look at all that loot.
Got all kinds of shit just now.
What's that?
Lost girl.
Hello.
Another NPC, maybe.
It does seem like danger though, doesn't it?
Why is there a danger icon on her?
I'm coming.
Oh, hello.
Medusa.
Excuse me.
Skeleton.
Why is my fucking cohort not doing shit?
Where's my weapon there?
Oh my god, I'm in a terrible position.
Oh, I have no mana.
That's what's happening.
Oh, there's a chest here.
So hold on, I'm going to check that later.
I can't fucking see when I'm zoomed out.
Oh, what?
I got turned to stone.
Medusa, huh?
It's true what they say then.
Oh, is it from that statue?
Wait a minute.
Ah, yep.
I was looking at that statue going.
What is, what is that even depict?
I can't quite tell.
Let's see here.
Oh, suspicious looking eye.
More of a hasty inner tube.
Where's the ability to float in water?
Wait, really?
It's exactly what I imagined.
That's so fucking silly.
Oh, man.
This looks so dumb.
I'm going to walk around with it though.
I feel like it's fitting.
Oh, did I just drop them all?
No, I didn't.
Where did this girl go?
Oh, wait, I was digging here.
I still have the gills.
Oh, well, only for a brief moment.
I'm coming.
Why do you have to arrive right when I'm doing the digging, huh?
There's somewhere down here.
It's draining time.
Drain the water.
Aquacola.
Hey, you like that?
What is that?
A giant bat.
Dude, everything is changed.
Look at this guy, 520 HP.
Is that what I...
Is that what I unleashed?
Did I unleash a slew of new monsters or something?
Is that what the guide was mentioning?
Where's this girl?
Girl?
Lost girl?
Get away from me.
Where art thou?
Hold on.
Where the hell?
Fuck, I looked away for a second.
And now, gone.
Did
she go further down, maybe?
Thanks.
What's that?
Pickaxe?
Hold on, I want to test something right now.
Is that increasing my...
No, it's the same.
I thought it actually increased my mining speed.
What?
Oh!
The map!
Treasure map, right?
Where?
Show me treasure.
Okay, maybe that's not what I think it is.
Give me this.
Okay, yeah, I want to keep going down.
Oh, wait, wait, that's actually the room there.
I want to grab that first.
Kind of spot...
I missed that completely.
Glow sticks.
Nah, nobody wants that.
That sucks.
Honestly, I can't get used to breathing on the water.
That would be terrible.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's that?
Bound wizard!
Excuse me?
Thanks for saving me, friend.
This bondage was starting to chafe.
Where's my house?
Where am I?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Reminds me of the old days of practicing magic up in a tower in the middle of nowhere.
Oh, that's what you want, huh?
You want to be in the tower in the middle of nowhere.
Say no more, fam.
I got you.
What do you sell?
A crystal bowl.
Ice rod.
Oh!
Greater mana potion.
A bell?
Harp?
They're all materials, by the way.
Music box.
Wait a minute.
Wasn't there an item that needed a crystal ball to be made?
I seem to have a memory of that.
Someone's a block of ice?
Dude, 75 gold?
That's a lot of money.
Money I don't have.
But you're gonna be making your way back to town, right?
No, he's going in the water.
Why are you...
What's that?
Ruby squirrel?
I just killed it.
No, don't kill him!
No, you motherfucker!
I just gotta respawn.
Everything's fine.
Fuck you all.
Oh, we're gonna drain so hard right now.
Drain gang, drain gang, drain gang.
Love to drain.
Love draining, dude.
Not to be confused with the love draining dudes.
That's another matter.
And I'm not affiliated with that.
Maylord the wizard has arrived.
Okay, he's already back.
Perfect.
Why am I digging this way?
Actually, I'm gonna go through this up here.
Whoa!
Oh, you're just a skeleton.
Okay.
Get away from me.
Now, where did he go?
He went to the main hub.
Perfect.
What do we got?
Oh, that's the same chest.
Oh, what's happening here?
Arm...
Possessed armor.
I do wonder if this guy dropped something amazing.
A sound came just now that went...
When I killed him.
Not sure what that means.
Maybe that's just his death roll.
His death rattle.
This is...
The molten pig act is great for this.
Wait!
Oh, I thought this was new.
Because it's like purple.
But it's not.
It just means it goes in the void bag.
I thought I just found something new here.
Oh my god.
Can you get away from me?
God damn.
Okay, this just connects back over here.
Maybe that's not a terrible idea.
I think there's got to be more underneath the ocean.
In any case, for now I'm going to head back.
I need to empty my shit.
And talk to the wizard.
He's right there.
Maylor.
Are you here for a peek at my crystal ball?
No sir, I do not want to see your ball.
Cool.
Let's not talk about that.
How much do I have in here?
Twenty-nine!
Not bad.
Let me see here.
Well, hi there, Fjell!
What can I do for you today?
Bro, you are suffering from something.
I'm not Fjell.
Never been.
I'll be taking that.
Thank you.
The greater...
I kind of want to buy this, but I don't have the money.
I'm going to be trying all these.
Uh, pip!
Mama always said I would make a great tailor.
Oh yeah?
Well, I don't know about that.
Wait a minute, didn't we have a thingy?
Shipton the traveling merchant.
Where are you?
Oh, you're out there.
Let's see what you got.
Shipton!
Don't have a look!
One pound fish.
Very, very good.
I can buy a fedora.
My lady.
Stopwatch.
Red cape.
Cattlegator!
Insanely fast speed.
Highly inaccurate.
Uh...
I kind of want it.
I don't even care.
Spend all my money.
This feels so terrible.
Spending all my money like this so recklessly.
But it also feels great, you know what I mean?
Spell tome!
Uh...
Okay.
Yep.
I can, uh...
Spray a shower of ichor.
I don't know how I feel about that.
Cursed flames.
Summons unholy fireballs.
Summons rapid fire cri- Wait a minute, crystal shards?
Aren't those the ones I need to make something?
A crystal shard.
Asher?
I need to know about...
Uh...
The crystal ball.
No!
Oh, I thought it was material!
Well, well, uh, you know what I want to do?
Fucking hell.
It's time.
I want to make...
Also, hold on.
Bestiary?
Where's the guy?
The wizard is an absent-minded, demented old man.
Yeah, I was about to say.
Who dabbles in the arcane arts.
He sells magical trinkets to train new apprentices.
He wants to be in the hallow.
What is the hallow?
Bro!
What?
What is the hallow?
Seth?
Asher, sorry, I keep calling you Seth.
Oh, man.
Honestly, I almost forgot what the name of the first guy was.
Was it Bob?
The very first one.
I actually forgot his name.
It's been so long ago.
Um...
Tell me some more, Asher.
Have you ever...
Yes, I have.
Make sure to smash any crimson altar you can find.
Something good is bound to happen if you do.
Right!
The own hammer is strong enough to destroy demon alt...
No, wait, demon altar is not the same as a crimson altar.
Is it?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute now.
Demon altar?
Demon al...
Demon altar.
Have I seen that?
Dude, I look so silly in this bathing ring.
Oh my god.
Let's just deposit some shit first.
You know what?
There's a million things I want to do, but I don't know in which order to do them.
You ever get that feeling?
Let's put a Medusa statue here.
Oh, Medusa, I call upon you.
So turn all these residents into stones so they may never...
...annoy me again.
Let's see if he...
Let's see if a Medusa spawns.
I'm gonna go down to the Crimson area and see if it actually works on that.
I have a suspicion it won't, and it will only work on actual...
Oh, hold on.
On demon altars, which I don't know what is.
Stop pulling about my tail, bro!
It's totally real and like totally hurts when you pull on it.
I'm not doing that.
You're fucking delusional.
Uh,
wait, oh yeah, you sell all kinds of stuff.
Mollusk whistle.
Leather whip.
Jousting!
Whoa!
This is new.
Jousting lands.
That's a lot of damage.
And it will be more damage.
The faster I move, it seems.
Maybe that can get up to ridiculous numbers if you go really fast.
Definitely worth experimenting with later on, but I don't have any money!
I kind of need to find some money.
Like really, I need money.
Also, you know what?
I want to...
So let me go here and check this out first.
We got to stay on track here.
And then I want to go see if the old man is there now.
I have unleashed something apparently, right?
Whoops.
Maybe the old man is involved.
I get the feeling that this area on the left here is kind of very important.
Uh, what did it say, Herpling?
I have unleashed Herplings.
Lotus, four...
Wait.
Oh, I'm shooting with the...
The Gattlegator.
Yeah.
It's not that great, is it?
Then again, I'm also optimized for magic damage right now.
So I can't really compare them apples to apples there.
Or apples to oranges.
I do like this laser.
Got it, feels good.
Cleanse this world.
Oh no, not that one.
Where's my, uh, saber?
Wow!
Whoa!
Okay, okay.
Bro, all right.
These guys don't fuck around.
Wow!
I got my ass handed to me.
We're taking the...
The highway.
Wait, what?
Excuse me?
What is that sound?
Oh, do you see the money on the minimap?
It disappeared.
Where did it go?
What is that sound?
Is it just the enemies?
The enemies pick up the money?
That's why I sometimes couldn't pick it up afterwards.
Are you fucking kidding me?
I saw it on the map and then it wasn't there.
And the first thing I thought of was Bloodborne.
If you know Bloodborne, you know what I'm talking about.
And then I went to check and I noticed.
Oh my god, these guys are very dangerous.
Oh my...
Wow!
Okay, these guys don't fuck around.
Get out of there.
Actually, no, I need to go back there because I need to go down there.
That was my whole mission.
Before I do anything else.
Leave me alone, leave me alone, leave me alone!
Money in.
Keep going.
Oh, I'm dying.
Oh my god, these guys are sick.
Why is this so difficult suddenly?
Shipton is gone.
Shipton has...
shift.
That was a terrible joke.
Don't laugh.
Okay.
No fucking around now, we go straight into the earth.
Can't even pronounce things anymore.
I'm so flabbergasted.
Wait.
All right, go quick before the enemies come.
Move it.
Here, let's try now.
Will it work?
Begone evil.
What?
Where?
Oh my god, I didn't get to click on it.
Okay, whatever.
Your world has been blessed with cobalt.
Huh?
Are you... are you saying that?
Wait a minute.
Your world has been blessed with orichalcum.
Okay.
I do like blessings.
Sounds to me like some kind of ore.
Uh, a wraith.
Dude, I have totally unleashed something in the world.
And it's all related to the guide.
Wait.
The wall of flesh.
Toxic... yeah, look, all these new enemies.
Your world has been blessed with titanium.
Yeah, look, these are all ores.
Are you saying the world contains new deposits of ore?
There's no way.
What the fuck?
There's something to the left here as well.
But I don't want to go there.
I want to find more of these altars.
Die!
Dude, I can't wait for a weapon that will penetrate like ground like this.
Imagine having such a weapon.
Probably would be a little overpowered, but I want it.
I want it.
Oh!
He died quick.
Oh, oh, these guys.
Oh my god, I'm so scared of them.
Dude, the Herplings are actually very problematic.
Bees!
Bro, is it just me or do the bees suck?
Call me crazy, but didn't they do more damage earlier on?
Maybe these enemies have more armor.
Oh god, don't kill me.
I'm actually dying here.
Also, it feels like these Herplings only spawn after a certain time.
After I've been down here.
It was clean of Herplings and now suddenly they're here.
Like, what gives?
You know what I mean?
Oh god, they're fast.
Yeah, I'm not having any of that.
Fuck.
Where do I want to go?
I can't really go anywhere.
Um...
Go!
Run!
Oh my god!
Dude, they're after me!
Where's my Earth?
There.
I need to block myself in.
We're back to the stratit- Oh.
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hold on.
Actually, this is not too bad.
Okay, this weapon kind of sucks now, right?
I feel like it's not really that great anymore.
It's falling behind here.
Ooh.
Cobalt!
Mind a powerful ore that has been newly blessed upon your world!
What the fuck?
Heck yeah, man!
Oh my god.
Are you kidding me?
Can we have more of those altars?
More, more, more.
Altars?
See, now the Herplings are gone.
Those bastards.
What do we got down here?
Okay, looks clean.
By the way, I just realized, maybe I should have left one of the altars alive.
Because you can actually use them to craft things.
Remember?
Oh, here they come!
The devils spawned!
Oh, here we go.
I'm taking it.
Your world has been blessed with- I wonder if- You hear that sound again?
What is that sound?
Does it happen every time I destroy an altar?
Let me try and pay attention.
There's another one here.
Your world has been- I wonder if it just blesses it with more.
Oh god.
Bam, bam.
Nice.
Get out of here.
Have I even been here?
Oh, I have, okay.
I've been blessed with even more.
I'm gonna leave one of these altars here.
Just in case I need it for later.
Like, can I take them with me now?
I don't think so.
Let me make a little path in here.
Oh god.
Look at all these new enemies.
What is that?
Possessed armor again.
So here's what I'm thinking.
Either it just increases the amount overall in the world whenever I do this, more, or a Calcum in general, or whenever it says world has been blessed with, it's actually only with a single deposit.
Imagine that.
That was, if that's the case, then the cobalt I found was very rare.
Hey.
My god, they have a lot of HP now.
I need to find better weapons.
If there's better enemies, bound to be better weapons.
That's empty.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Let's try out this cobalt.
Also, I want to try the crystal ball.
Let me put that in...
in the mage's quarter.
Put it...
Get rid of that.
There we go.
Let's see.
Clavoins.
Magic powers are increased.
Oh!
Wait, really?
67?
Oh, it's not magic damage.
It's magic powers.
So spells and shit.
Want some magic candy?
No?
Okay.
Don't ever ask me that again.
But yes, I would like some magic candy.
Give me a bell.
Give me a harp.
Give me a greater map.
I need to talk to Ashton.
Is that your name?
Asher.
Right.
Asher, what can I do with this?
A magical harp.
It's a...
Wait, it's a weapon.
Huh.
All right.
A fairy bell summons a magical fairy.
I guess it's another...
follower you can have that will deal damage.
Dude, I have all kinds of shit in my bags.
Where's that ore?
Tungsten, gold...
Clay...
Oh, did it go in my thingy?
Sword.
Man, where did it go?
You heard that?
Did the...
I'll just say...
What the fuck?
Cobalt, there it is.
It's a material.
Asher.
Cobalt bars, of course.
It makes sense.
Let's do it.
Ooh, okay.
Uh, what can I do with a cobalt bar, Asher?
Oh my god, here we go.
Fourteen!
Oh my god.
A drill?
Can mine Mithril and Orichalcum?
Cobalt...
Yes.
Okay, I know what the immediate goal is.
We gotta go mining.
Immediately.
Right now.
Stop everything.
We're going.
Deposit all.
Even the key.
I don't care.
We're going.
Where's the thingy?
Oh yeah, I also wanted to check that real quick.
Let's do that really quickly.
Cobalt bars, come with me.
Cobalt ore stays here as well.
Uh, ancient chisel?
Perfect.
Now, didn't I also have a mining potion?
You know what?
Just grab some stuff here.
Feather fall...
What's in here?
Only gold.
Nice.
And a platinum.
Man, I keep thinking this is silver.
It's messing with my head.
I want to make a mage tower for the wizard as well.
Think of the ones from World of Warcraft.
That's what I want to make.
I love those.
Greater mana.
Wait, restores 300 mana?
That would suggest maybe we can upgrade our mana even more.
Unless it simply means that you can attain 300 mana when you have the right gear.
That's also a thing.
Maybe that's the point here.
It's possible.
Let's put that shit in there.
Sort.
Okay, okay.
It's digging time.
No, wait, not yet.
Not yet.
First.
Water!
I need water!
Ah, where did I put it?
Vassa?
What happened to Vassa?
Okay, good.
Mahon?
No, no, no.
I want to ask you about things.
Now, the mining.
Let's see if I...
I remember the icon for this.
I will go straight on it when I see it.
There.
See?
Blink root and antlion.
Mandible.
I think I have both of those.
Antlion mandible.
Do I also have the mythical...
Blink root?
I have, like, 40 of them, have I not?
Somewhere.
Vine.
They put it in one of these random-ass chests.
That would be very bad of me to do, because that's an organic, and that's against the rules to do such a thing.
Are they in here?
They are in there!
God damn.
Okay.
All right.
Let's make it.
Mining.
Make all of them.
And then click this sweet button.
Does nothing, of course.
Antlion in here.
Blink root.
There, yeah.
All right.
Dig in we go.
Where do we dig?
I'm okay.
I almost fell out of my chair for some reason.
Uh, hold on.
Think.
We need to...
I can't do...
My character looks so fucking dumb.
But I love it!
I love the way he looks.
Hold on.
Lulan!
Demon horns.
Birdie rattle.
A magic hat.
Oh!
Yo!
That's not bad.
Oh, but it's an actual hat.
It's not like a hat pretending to be an accessory or the other way around, I mean.
Fuck.
Then I lose my ability to...
Actually, hold on.
This one is better.
I'm an idiot.
Okay, I'm gonna wear this.
Oh yeah, yeah.
Look at that.
This beautiful, beautiful stuff.
I actually have a bunch of things here.
I can't forget this.
I have a bunch of accessories in my other loadouts.
Let's remember that if I'm lost one day.
And I can't find my shit.
Which is pretty much all the time.
Okay.
My plan was to use a potion that would let me see treasure.
Right?
If we go find ore, we gotta use that.
And we gotta find cobalt first, so we can make the pickaxe, so we can mine ore calcum.
I'm probably not pronouncing that right.
But that's okay.
It is what it is.
Do I even have that potion?
Spillunker?
Yeah, I have it.
So the question is, where should we mine?
Honestly, I say...
How about...
underneath the house?
We just explore more caves here.
How about that?
Seems good to me.
Oh yeah.
Let's just keep going right beneath the commune.
Go deeper.
Oh, is that it?
My god!
Look at that jackpot already.
How incredible is that?
Let's use the potion.
And the mining.
And this.
What was this?
Don't do it.
Spillunker.
Will I be able to tell?
It's like it has a yellow overlay now, so it's kind of hard.
Oh, that looks new.
The green stuff?
Let's check it out.
Oh my god, we're so fast.
Oh yeah!
Hey, it's cobalt!
So the green stuff is cobalt, when you have this potion on.
Nice!
Oh yeah.
Oh, this is great.
I feel great.
How are you feeling today, huh?
If you...
And yeah, I'm talking to you.
Yeah, you.
Are you doing great today?
Are you having a blast on this Friday?
I hope you are.
Because I am.
And if we both could have a blast, it would be even better.
Did I tell you to...
Come here.
Stop.
What was that sound?
Mushy ladybug.
Are you the ones making sounds?
Ooh!
Oh!
Look at this bouncing off!
Oh yeah, this weapon sucks now.
What the fuck?
But I...
It's like the only weapon I have, though.
It doesn't use mana right now.
At least with the gear I have right now.
What is this?
Lead.
Okay.
Anomura fungus.
Nice.
There we go.
We got more up here.
And then we have an armored skeleton there.
Oh my god, I'm mining it so quick.
Feels great.
Hey, you there!
There's almost no knockback.
Oh, what's...
Oh, I'm confused.
I had to walk the opposite way there to go left.
That was very unintuitive.
Oh!
Falling mud!
So tanky.
I definitely need new weapons, man.
I need crazy weapons to deal with this BS.
I require the strongest weapons.
Oh!
That's a bit of a top spot there.
Let's go the other way.
What is that?
Oh, it's water.
Look like something else.
Look like some kind of... I don't even know.
Like a basin.
What the...
Oh, I have been in here before.
Doesn't it look very different?
I feel like everything here is very different looking too.
What is that?
Tungsten, right?
Can we get some more of that cobalt?
Oh!
Precise shoe spikes.
Dynamite archery.
Reeball, torch, sure.
What is that?
Dragonfly statue.
Yeah, just put it.
Terrarian Gothic.
Hold on, that looks special up there.
Also, there's a trap there.
I see it.
Was that the new one?
No, that was titanium, wasn't it?
Oh, there's some nasty...
Ooh, is that the famous orichalcum?
Oh, that hurt.
Let's check it out, huh?
Ow!
Keep getting sand in my eyes.
Look at the sandy water.
That's very not nice.
Oh my god, 640 HP.
Whew, what is that?
Oh, right, it's these things.
They're somehow even more tangy now.
Horrible stuff.
Oh no, wait, this is desert fossil.
Oh, I don't want to go down there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's a bad idea.
Gimme this.
I'm not done exploring here.
We gotta find some more cobalt.
Let me keep going over here.
I've had more success in this general area, I feel like.
Actually, yeah, go down.
Go down a bit.
Ah, there we go.
And there we go.
Nice.
I need to make more scarab bombs.
Actually, do I?
I'm so fast right now.
No props.
I think I have enough cobalt to make the pickaxe.
So I'm gonna make it.
Ooh, hello.
Oh no.
Oh, wait a minute.
I must have looted this.
Yeah, that's not a lot of cobalt here, but I will take it.
Now, this also looks interesting down there.
Oh, look how fast I'm digging.
It's so pleasant.
What is this?
Tin.
Oh.
Oh, look at that over there.
It's red.
Let's not die here.
Is that orichalcum?
Or titanium.
Let's check it out.
Llewellyn has departed.
That's fine.
Oh, yeah, this has to be okay.
Yeah, yeah, this is either orichalcum or titanium.
Let's go back.
Let's make a pickaxe here.
Zoom in a bit.
Click this button, because it's awesome.
And then ours.
Cobalt.
Fuck yeah.
And then...
Oh, here we go.
The drill.
Should I make a pickaxe or a drill?
Mythril.
What is the difference?
I'm making this.
I had to sneeze there.
I'm sorry.
I just dug a hole in the middle of my house.
Dude, the allergies are kicking my ass right now.
This is ri- Oh, no.
Wood.
There we go.
Everything's back to normal.
I like the drill.
It's damaged though.
Let's repair it.
Why do you look all sick?
Wait a minute.
What was I doing just now?
I was gonna repair.
Oh, but wait, he's not here.
He's at the other place.
Let me quickly go talk to him.
He is...
Hold on, Dante.
What do you sell?
You sell new things.
20% chance to save ammo.
Shotgun.
Dude.
I...
It's a material.
No way.
Oh, I don't have any bullets.
Wait a minute.
Let me just quickly try.
Let's buy like 10 of these.
Oh!
Oh my god.
Close range?
This is actually sick.
What the fuck?
Are you kidding me?
And it's a material.
Oh my god, hold on.
Asher!
Asher...
Kutcher.
Look at this here.
Onyx blaster.
Dark shard.
Sometimes carried by creatures in dark deserts.
Oh, like during the night?
I still need soul of night.
The essence of dark creatures.
I wonder if there is some kind of tool I can use to extract soul or sorry essence from different enemies to get these different variations of soul.
I mean, I got soul of light, I think.
From a boss.
But it's only one.
Which is kind of nuts.
I need more.
Anyway, what I'm thinking of is the extractor thingy from World of Warcraft again.
The thing that extracts modes of air and stuff, you know.
Modes of fire and all that.
From those clouds.
Um, why do I have an iron anvil on me?
Wait, did I?
Oh, wait!
It was here, wasn't it?
I was about to delete it.
Let me see what else I can make with this cobalt.
Increased movement speed.
I honestly, I gotta try and make this just to see what the set bonus is.
20 plus 15 plus 10.
Oh, I can make that.
Let's just do it.
But hold on.
Chainsaw?
Oh, it's for felling trees, I guess.
Cobalt sword, the naginata.
War axe.
Now, let's make the gear.
I want to see what the set bonus is.
14% reduced mana costs.
Oh!
Wait!
Wait a minute!
Uh, didn't this say something else?
Am I crazy?
Didn't it say melee something?
10% increased ranged damage.
Look at this!
Oh, oh!
Oh, I get it!
There's three different helmets!
I was like, maybe the game auto detected that I was going for magic damage and it automatically put that on it instead of the other one.
But there's three helmets here.
That's a- okay, okay, I see now.
Oh!
Great!
That's exactly what I want!
Beautiful!
And this is like, significantly better.
But it doesn't give me infinite ammo on my thingy, of course.
But that's fine, but I'm using laser rifle now anyway.
Oh yeah, it drains much slower.
Doesn't it?
Does it actually drain slower?
Yeah.
Also, I have more total mana as well.
That also helps.
That's awesome.
But honestly, I also kind of want to shotgun things.
That seems great as well.
So, I could- so- Oh!
Ah, okay, wait a minute.
So if I were to make the helmet that gave ranged damage, I think the set bonus would be different.
The set bonus would be made for guns, and bows, and stuff like that.
That is how that works.
This is a crazy upgrade I just did.
Fuck the meteor stuff!
Nobody wants that shit!
In you go!
Actually, don't put it there.
Put it over here, among the other thingies I have.
There, there, and there.
Okay!
Honestly, I want to sell these arrows.
I don't use the arrows.
Arrows?
Will they even pay for it?
Where did they go?
What?
Oh, did I put them in here?
What did I just- Oh yeah, I did.
Ah, okay.
All right, sell.
Sir!
Buy my arrows.
They're taking up slots, and I don't like it.
Okay, now, I kind of want to get rid of this now.
I want to get rid of this as well.
I wonder, this one says able to mine Hellstone.
This one does not.
Is it just implied that this one can also mine Hellstone?
That's what I'm wondering.
I guess I'll find out.
And for now, I'm going to keep this.
Just in case.
I mean, maybe this one is specially made only for Hellstone, you know?
The meteor hammax is also kind of trash now, because I have the own hammer.
Demon altars.
I wonder why it says demon altars and not crimson altars.
Maybe a crimson altar is a subset of demon altars.
Maybe there's multiple variations of these altars around the world.
And altogether, they're considered demon altars.
You know?
That's what would make sense.
Okay, put this in here.
No, don't put that there.
Put this over here instead.
There, there.
Put all this stuff in here for now.
I know it's not very sorted.
It's shit.
It really is shit my sorting right now.
I feel like I should fix that.
Like right now.
But I also want to go play with my new toy.
My new armor set and stuff.
And also, I found something like this.
Lucky trifold map.
Let me talk to Ash and Kutcher here.
What could I make?
The plan.
The plan?
Fast clock.
Wait a minute.
Clock.
Haven't I seen that already?
Was it a traveler who sold it?
Someone sold a clock.
Wait a minute.
Could it be Ella?
He's like very mechanical, right?
Dante keeps talking about pressing my pressure plate.
I told him it was for stepping on.
Huh.
Okay, let's see here.
Wait, teleporter?
Hold on.
No.
Wait a minute.
There's no way.
They're activating.
Look at this.
There's an animation there.
Do we need something special for this?
Maybe it's just like Minecraft.
You put a lever next to it.
Let's try.
Ha ha ha.
I do love the sound that makes.
Wait a minute.
Why is it lighting up like that?
Oh!
It's because I had the smart cursor on.
I see.
Okay.
Does it need to be connected first?
Like directly.
Places...
But hold on.
Don't I already have one of those?
I do.
Places...
Wire.
I actually never really tried this stuff.
Oh wait, I don't have any wire.
I need to buy wire first.
I think that's where...
I think I tried this, but I...
I realized something similar.
Okay, let's try this.
Oh right, I need to do...
I need to do this.
Huh.
The wire is gone now.
Dude, the wire cost five silver for that little point.
I feel like that's a little steep.
Am I crazy?
Let's try that.
Oh, wait a minute, maybe...
Oh, hold on now.
Maybe I need to connect these two together with a wire, huh?
Oh wait, I need to use this.
Oh my god, I'm already out.
Uh, but actually it's...
Oh, wait, what happened?
Oh!
Oh, it's invisible.
Oh, okay.
I see how this works.
It's like invisible.
Oh, that's actually kind of neat.
It's like redstone, but invisible redstone that you can only see while you have in the builder mode.
Buy 10 more of this.
Okay, uh,
hopefully I can...
Wait.
Ah, there we go.
Oh, and this one is still...
Ah, okay, so it's not gone.
Okay, also there was an option.
There was a tool that removed the wire, right?
How do I connect it?
Like that?
Wait a minute.
Maybe I need...
Hold on now.
Let's get a wire cutter.
Let's try a...
I don't even know.
Creates measurement lines on screen for block placement.
Wait, what is the difference?
Oh, place is blue.
There's different colors of wire as well.
Let me try something else.
Do I get it back?
Ah, and it counts as ammo.
Oh, that's actually really nice.
Oh, oh, that's fast as well.
Nice.
Let me put equip these like that.
Let me try something else.
Let me try this.
Like that.
And then we use this.
Okay, I have an idea.
I have an idea.
I think we should...
Because the teleporter seems a little complicated.
Maybe we should try and experiment with the wires on something more simple first.
Just to see if we can actually understand that part.
Grant's improved wire vision.
What?
Oh!
Wait, what?
You get to see the wire anytime now.
Instead of only when you have the wrench equipped.
No, wait, wait, what?
Why can I still see it?
Huh?
Look, now it's gone.
Now it's there.
Wait, does it work from the inventory?
Is that what I'm seeing here?
Like if I...
Wait.
You're not telling me these work from the inventory.
Oh my god.
Oh no, wait, that's not the thing.
That's this one.
Wait a minute.
Why does this work from the inventory?
What?
Does this work from the inventory?
No, it doesn't.
How do I know what...
That's so weird.
Do some of these work...
without needing to have them equipped?
I don't think they do, because I would have noticed.
But this one does.
That's very inconsistent.
What the hell?
Like, look!
I don't need to have this equipped.
It's as equipable, I can have it equipped if I want to, but I don't need to.
It's here.
Look, I can see the wire.
There's a gold bunny there.
It's dead now.
Whatever.
Let me try something else.
Maybe this wire needs to come from below.
Oh!
It's sort of automatically linked there.
Oh yeah, right.
I wanted to try something simpler first.
Hold on.
What can I try this on?
Can I do something simple, like opening a door?
Start off with here.
I thought I could pet Ella for a second there.
That was a bit weird.
Let's see.
Enable solid blocks to be toggled on and off.
Activates when a projectile touches it.
Activates and breaks when a player steps on it.
Lights up bulbs for each...
Oh.
Let's try that.
Wire bulb.
I can just put it anywhere.
So let's do this.
Oh yeah, yeah, look.
It's totally connected.
Is it?
Whoops.
Wait.
Oh, this one.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
I cannot figure out my key bindings.
I suck.
It's working!
Look!
Okay, okay.
Okay.
How close do we need to be here?
Let's see.
Not yet.
Now.
It just needs to physically, or not physically, visually touch the object, I think.
So I think I did it right here.
Before.
But I think they definitely need to be connected by a wire.
That would make the most sense to me.
So.
No, let's do one less.
They are connected now.
Now I just need to find a way to activate them.
Are these just cosmetic?
There's no way, right?
There's no way they would be cosmetic.
I mean, a lot of stuff is, but of all things, there's no way this is.
It's just so nonchalant, you know?
Like, oh, by the way, there's a teleporter.
No information, just teleporter.
So like, does it actually teleport me?
From one place to another, molecularly disassemble me, and put me somewhere else?
Fuck.
It's gotta work.
Let me try a switch.
Maybe there's a difference.
Maybe these don't work like that.
I love the sound of the drill.
Let's...
Okay.
Let's try this now.
Let's connect, let's connect all of this.
Oh, wait, I need to.
Oh, I have no more wire.
Oh, wait, I have an idea.
Um, no, let me get more wire anyway.
Yeah, let me get that wire.
Let's get a bit more here.
Let's get...
25.
Just a bit of playing around wire here.
Oh my god, it works!
That scared the crap out of me!
Dude, I fucking jumped back in my seat just now.
Hey!
It works!
Fucking fantastic!
Wait, why didn't it work with the...
Oh, okay now.
Okay!
So it is...
It is the...
So if I do that...
Not working.
Oh my god, okay.
So that's the limitation here.
If I want to be teleporting around, I need to lay down some wire.
And I mean a lot.
I see.
But dude!
This could be used.
Over here.
Teleporter here.
Plop, pop down, down here.
Oh my god, that would be my ideal solution.
Where I wanted to fully immerse this structure in the liquid.
Right?
That would be the thing.
Okay!
Okay, dude!
That's awesome!
Nice!
Ella!
I could kiss you right now, but I'm not gonna.
I kind of want the helmet now.
I feel like I deserve that helmet.
I feel like I completed the engineering education.
I have now activated the teleporter.
I know how it works.
Yep.
Let's put some stuff in here.
Let's put all this stuff in here.
This is gonna be the redstone box.
Chicken nugget!
Why do I have one of these here?
Let me also equip this stuff here.
And where's my...
Yeah, you know what?
I think the gray sapinator.
I think it's time for that to be discarded.
I don't like it.
It's sort of bad now.
Yeah.
I think so.
Alright!
What's next?
Let me talk to Ashton.
You should stay indoors at night.
No, I shouldn't.
Souls can sometimes be gathered from fallen creatures in places of extreme light or dark.
Okay!
Extreme light or dark?
There's only one place.
Wait a minute.
When you say extreme light or dark, are you saying I need to physically kill creatures in areas with no light, meaning do not place a torch?
Is that what you're saying?
Anyway, there's only one place here where I can...
Well, that popped into my mind just now.
I'm going there.
And it is, of course, the retirement home where the old man resides.
Or did reside.
I don't know what the fuck happened to him.
Well, yeah.
Also, let's...
Oh, let's not do that right now.
Spillunker?
Nido?
And mining, I'm going to activate when I'm there.
Oh, wait!
Did I ever make mine?
Oh, yeah, I did.
Now I can go find the orichalcum.
That's actually what I wanted to do.
I can probably find some more of it somewhere.
Let's just keep going.
I want to check out this place again.
Place of extreme light could mean up here, right?
In heaven.
Wait, give me this again.
Whoa.
Thank you.
Oh, look at that.
There's wire here.
My God, I should have brought my cutters.
I do remember playing around with a button here.
That's amazing.
Someone wired the dungeon.
They had an electrical guy out here.
There's something funny about that.
Wait, can I actually get through this?
Oh, yeah, I can.
Green brick.
Hold on, let me actually zoom out a bit and see if I can find some valuables.
Oh, this guy has a lot of HP.
Jesus, I need a new weapon.
This is terrible.
Am I seeing anything good?
Oh, there's something red over there.
Oh, wiring.
Who's wiring in the dark?
Oh, oh, look at that.
What's happening here?
What's that?
Cursed skull.
Oh, what the hell?
Hold on, let me try.
Ah, you can totally spot traps like this.
That's...
explosions.
Come on, come here.
Please die.
Oh my god, it's not dead yet.
There we go.
Okay, I'll take...
This is the explosion that has been fucking me up.
Can I mine this?
Wait a minute, what actually...
I'm not sure what that is.
Is this going to blow up?
Let's do some testing.
Open this, put it in.
Ah, fuck!
Okay, I need bolt cutters and I need to...
Fuck, oh man, that's actually kind of cool.
It's just like a bomb defusal team.
I have to grab my bolt cutter or like my wire cutter and I have to cut the right wire here not to blow shit up.
Ah, man.
All right, well, at least that's confirmed.
Give me that.
Kind of a useful item now.
All right, back we go.
Okay.
Also, I don't think I've been able to mine the walls of this place.
Up until now.
Oh!
You hear that?
Who's making that sound?
Oh no, it's these things.
I hate them.
Places of extreme dark?
Could this be considered one of them?
Oh my god, I need mana!
Oh my god, I'm out of mana.
I need another weapon.
This is just not reliable enough.
Like, if you run out of... yeah, then it's over.
Oh my god, this is horrible.
Now we're leaving.
We're gonna... we're gonna figure out what that sound is next time.
Not right now.
I need to find some nice weapons here.
I do wonder if that chest... if there's even loot in there or if it's just a trap and that's it.
If I diffuse the trap, can I get loot or not?
Or is the chest just filled with explosives, you know?
That's what I'm wondering.
Because whatever was in that chest, I don't think I can get it anymore.
That shit is gone.
Oh, let me see here.
Yeah, I can totally remove all this.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Thank you.
It's such a weird place.
Okay, the chest is still there.
Is it gonna blow up again?
Okay, here we go.
Get rid of... actuator.
Solid blocks to be toggled on or off.
So, wait.
Was everything below and around the chest explosives then that was toggled on by this?
It's gotta be fine now, right?
Yeah!
Cool.
Angel statue?
I'm gonna try and place one of those on an island.
Dead man's sweater.
Why is it... why is there a dead man's sweater?
The man died.
What's that?
Oh, that's nothing.
I didn't see that.
That is nothing at all.
Nothing, I tell you.
Let's have a hunter and a spelunker.
All right, it's time to find...
There it is.
Well, it's not this I wanted, but I'll take it.
Oh, yeah, it's so quick.
Did I use the mining?
Not yet.
Oh, this is gonna be so quick.
Okay, the drill sound does get a little old quite fast.
Maybe it will make a pickaxe instead.
It was cool the first time I heard it, you know?
But now I'm like, I don't know about that.
We may have to change our mind on that one.
Ah, get away from me, stupid monsters.
I don't want to fight.
Can we just get along?
Peace.
I require peace.
Diddle it, diddle it, diddle it, diddle it.
Oh, yeah, look.
This requires a key with a red stone inlaid and a yellow or golden handle thingy.
And this is like...
Can I use the...
No, okay.
I don't think the old man is...
Oh, look at that.
There's a thingy in there.
What the hell?
Angry bones.
What is that?
Oh, it's just loot thingies.
Get away.
I shall be destroying this.
Bless with titanium.
Once again.
Maybe there's just more of it now.
That...
You know what?
That's what I think.
I think there's just more of it.
Which is nice.
Why did this guy get confused?
He didn't even hit me.
What am I seeing there?
Now, you know what?
Let's not be down here.
I changed my mind.
I'm going back down to where I know there's orichalcum.
Or titanium.
It was somewhere down there.
Give me it.
I can't wait to see what I can make with titanium or orichalcum.
Maybe I can make a great new weapon.
That's like my number one goal right now, is to figure out a way to make better weapons.
Because god damn, my weapons suck.
It's not good.
Zoom out all the way so I can see all the loot.
Where was I?
Where did I find this?
Was it over here?
Oh, I don't even have my thingy on.
Oh, I did.
No, I'm an idiot.
Fuck.
I just didn't see any, so I just assumed.
God damn it.
That was a mistake.
There's actually a chest over there.
Let's check.
Oh, let's check that out, actually.
Let's move carefully here.
Let's not let everything fall on our heads.
Whoops.
Oh my god.
Use the magic missile.
Whoa, watering dune rider boots.
Wait, walk without rhythm and you won't attract the worm?
I feel like that's a reference to something.
Yeah, drink that.
Delete that.
Delete that and take that.
Thank you very much.
I'm invisible now.
What is that?
Lamia!
Uh, hello.
Oh my god, 700 HP.
Do you drop anything nice?
Oh, we got cobalt.
Yahoo!
There's chests below us and there's stuff above us.
No, wait, that's just sand stuff.
Magic conch.
If you listen closely, you can hear the ocean.
Oh yeah?
Slime is falling from the sky.
I don't have room for shit.
Uh, fill it up.
Nice.
I don't want that.
I want this.
I want that.
I want to try and give this to Ashton.
What is that?
Oh, right.
Man, look at all the enemies here.
Oh, he's dying in lava now.
That's nice.
Oh, look at that.
That's it right there.
That's it.
Hup.
Bad idea.
Orykalkum.
There it is.
Get away from me.
Oh my god.
Get away.
What are you?
Ghoul.
There's enemies everywhere here.
This is dangerous territory.
Wow, look at all the enemies.
I see more Orykalkum.
Give me that mana.
Oh my god, that's a big one!
Dunesplizer.
I should have worn the sand boots.
I should have walked arithmically.
Rookie mistake.
Shit.
That's okay.
I actually wanted to get back anyway.
Yeah, this is a speedrunner strat.
Just dying to get back.
Okay, Mr. Asher.
If you defeat enough of these slimes, you might invoke the wrath of their king.
Be careful.
Oh yeah, I actually did.
You know what?
Let's do it again.
Let's see if we can get some new loot.
Um, hold on.
What?
No.
Open this.
Look.
No!
Look in that.
I have potions in here.
Give me that as well.
Not...
Yeah, sure.
All of that.
Thorns.
Okay.
I'm going to try and murder slimes now.
Maybe there's something new, because we unleashed everything, right?
These slimes are also harder to kill, I think.
They have like...
Yeah, they have way more HP.
Why don't you want to bet?
There's a different boss now.
Oh, zoom out.
There we go.
Kill them all.
In fact, hold on.
Let me summon.
There we go.
Blue slime banner.
Dude, speaking of bosses, I wonder if anything new happens when I summon this now.
I feel like I should get better items, right?
To deal with the better enemies.
Why am I so...
If I'm to do this, I kind of need different weapons here.
My weapons kind of suck.
Honestly, the magic missile is still...
the best for me, because it's not using as much mana.
I don't have to aim or think.
I just press a button.
You know?
Like, I just do like this.
Let me put this here.
Green slime.
I should put these banners down, actually.
And I also have another banner.
And even faster on sand.
Where's the other one?
Did I get two banners just now?
Yeah, this is not that great.
Magic missile, dude, is where it's at.
Here we go!
King slime.
Looks like it's the same thing, though.
That's fine.
Maybe I get new loot.
See, I'm out of mana already, because I used that weapon now.
So now I'm like...
Really oom.
Oh wait, I don't have infinite...
Oh, hold on, I don't...
Oh.
Hey!
Dude!
Yo, this is sick!
Hey, I'm a slime too!
What you gonna do about it?
You ain't gonna do shit about it!
Oh my god!
Hey, yeah!
This is incredible.
Come on, get rid of these slimes.
I have to fait it!
It's a slime.
Let's see what I got.
Uh, let's...
Oh, inventory is completely full here.
Deposit all.
What did I get?
Didn't I?
Wait.
Huh?
Am I blind?
What did I...
What did I just get?
Did I get a...
Huh?
Did he go in here?
No.
Oh, it went in there!
Oh!
Okay.
That explains it.
Let's see.
A ninja hood.
A slime hook and another solidifier.
All right.
Well, it was worth a try.
Worth a try.
Not the biggest...
Let me put this somewhere here.
Where should I put it?
Put it outside.
Oh my god.
Get rid of this!
God damn it.
There we go.
You can be there.
Ninja pants and ninja hood.
Hold on, actually.
Don't I have the last part as well?
Ninja...
Ninja shirt.
Let me see if there's a set bonus on this one.
Wait.
Shirt.
Hood.
20% increased movement speed.
Hey!
That's pretty cool.
Awesome.
But I do like this more.
I do like that more.
But kind of cool nonetheless, though.
Let me put that in here for now.
What else did I get?
Slime hook.
All righty.
Cobalt.
Oh, where did I put the cobalt?
Put it in here.
Sort.
And where did I put the cobalt?
Put it in here.
It is.
There it is.
Now, give me cobalt bars.
I also had orichalcum.
Where did that go?
Probably also in here.
There it is.
It kind of looks like a gem, doesn't it?
Orichalcum bar.
Asher.
Let's see about this.
Orichalcum anvil.
Used to craft items from Mithril, Orichalcum adamantide and titanium bars.
Okay.
Oh my gosh!
Nineteen defense.
Oh, but that's for melee.
Or melee.
Oh, this is actually...
Oh, that's very little defense when you're...
Okay.
It's better than what I have.
Increase magic.
This also increases damage, though.
Probably the set bonus is also different.
Dude, you know what?
This is awesome.
Oh!
Orichalcum repeater.
I think I may want to try and go range it.
And not magic.
I do like the sound of gunfire.
You know?
And it doesn't cost mana.
And I also get a bit more defense.
And increased movement speed.
See, that's nice.
I like to be mobile.
That seems like a good thing.
I could also try to go melee.
There's so many things I want to...
I want to try it all!
Is that crazy?
I want to do all of it.
Look at all the stars up here.
My goodness.
Give me all that.
Thank you.
Okay.
Well.
That's it for now.
Because I need to eat!
I've been putting that off.
I was like, should I eat a little bit before?
And I was like, ah, no.
I'm going to save it until I'm really hungry.
And now I'm hungry.
Hold on.
Leaf!
Hey, man.
I think I missed you joining.
If you're here, welcome.
Thanks for joining the potato.
The straight line.
Thank you.
Esanti, once again.
Five euros.
Amazing stream today.
Nice!
Thank you.
Yeah, I think so too.
It was really fun.
Fantastic stream.
Have a good one.
You too, Jorik.
See you around.
Congrats on killing Wuff.
Wall of flesh.
Ah, right.
Thank you.
Yeah, dude.
That took me so long.
I was getting a little frustrated with that boss at some point.
It was just like, come on.
But I did it.
I freaking did it.
Dear Dops.
Yeah, the C and the L kind of looked like a D in this game because of the font.
Congrats on wall of flesh.
Glad to have seen it live.
Thank you so much, Hegular.
And thanks for the donation.
Like his comment, people.
Apparently, that's a thing now.
You can like donations.
I just noticed.
Isn't that new?
Thank you, Hegular.
I hope you become a regular.
That was the most controversial stream.
It was a lot of progress, yet so stupid.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
GG on beating the wall of flesh.
Thanks, Enzo.
Thank you so much.
My first time joining stream to say hi.
Been loving this series.
Thank you, SeesetU or Seesu.
I appreciate that as well.
Thank you for the kind words.
I can't believe it only took 13 streams.
Yeah, Friday the 13th stream.
Not the day, the 13th stream on a Friday.
Everything was stacked against me on this day, but I succeeded.
Glad I've been able to witness it.
Nice.
Oliver, how many streams do you think Terrario will take?
Honestly, I have no clue.
I thought the game would sort of be over in a way.
Well, I don't think this game truly ends if I were to guess it.
But I thought I was like, okay, it's sort of done after the wall of flesh.
But it seems that's not the case.
There's like more things happening.
So honestly, I have no good answer for that question.
I don't know.
Could be anything.
I have started to...
I'm just gonna give up on trying to answer that question.
Oliver, mind sharing what you're going to be eating?
I'm going to be eating some...
What is the English word for that?
A pork chop with some salad.
And the salad is going to be just a mixed salad with some grapes, green grapes in there, some tomato, and some feta cheese.
It's the best fucking salad.
It's so good.
And the reason for eating that is because that's what I have left.
You were peeking until you were not.
I feel like that's usually the case with me.
Or it's the other way around, you know?
I was not peeking until I was.
Or usually it's not peeking until I peek until I don't, you know?
And then it just reverses and keeps going.
I'm also going to make food.
Always fun watching it, boy.
Thanks, JD.
I feel like you've been here forever too, right?
I just remember your profile picture.
I don't know who that is.
But for some reason, it cracks me up.
Your profile picture is hilarious, JD.
Thanks for sticking around.
So how many percent do you think you are?
All the percents.
Out of even more percents.
All through on that leftovers diet.
Bro, the leftovers diet is the best diet.
It's so good.
A gem of a game.
Nice.
Good one, Justice P. Quasi-manipulation.
That's a cool name.
Really glad you're taking your time with this game.
Yeah, I'm in no rush.
I'm enjoying it.
Honestly, I want to do more of the building sessions.
That's been so much fun making those houses.
I can't wait to build a mage tower for the wizard.
I'm going to put a crystal ball in there.
It's going to look amazing.
Oh yeah, I have plants.
Big plants.
Do we have another inscription episode today?
Yeah, actually, as soon as I end the stream, I'm going to release it.
Because I didn't want to overlap while the stream was going, you know?
So yeah, I'm going to release it within probably five minutes.
People are loving that series, by the way.
It's been doing really well.
The building streams were nice.
I think so too.
Retro real.
Retro real?
I'm going to call you retro real, okay?
That's how I pronounce your name from now on.
Which in Danish means the retro cupboard.
You are a piece of furniture and you're retro and you're cool.
Okay, guys, I'm going to be out of here and eat some food.
You guys have a great Friday.
Thanks for checking this stream out.
It's so cool to talk with you guys about it afterwards.
And it is kind of cool knowing people are watching while you discover all these funny things, you know?
When something really funny happens or something, it's cool to know that it's shared among many people.
So yeah, have a good night and enjoy your weekend, damn it.
You deserve it.
And go out and touch grass because the weather is nice.
Bye-bye.